<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[aside]]></title>
  <link href="http://sidesix.org//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sidesix.org//"/>
  <updated>2012-01-10T15:43:34-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://sidesix.org//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Daniel Avery]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To The New Aside]]></title>
    <link href="http://sidesix.org//blog/2012/01/10/welcome-to-the-new-aside/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-10T14:55:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sidesix.org//blog/2012/01/10/welcome-to-the-new-aside</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I had a blog on this site before, when I was using Expression Engine as the cms for this site. But I didn&#8217;t write much. It wasn&#8217;t because I don&#8217;t have anything to say about creativity, the creative process, web design, and so on. Expression Engine didn&#8217;t play nice with Mars Edit, which I used to write blog posts in markdown. It ended up being a pain in the ass and I don&#8217;t do well when something is a pain in the ass.  That is why I&#8217;ve always used Apple products rather than the pc variety.</p>

<p>When I decided to make this site responsive, I started to look around at other solutions.  I had recently stumbled onto a couple of static site generators. I&#8217;m sure they&#8217;ve been around quite a while, but I am starting to teach myself ruby and rails. When I saw <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a> I knew I had found my blog engine. We&#8217;ll see how it goes, but I&#8217;m hopeful.  This guy <a href="http://brandonmathis.com/">Brandon Mathis</a> also is responsible for <a href="http://brandonmathis.com/projects/fancy-buttons/">fancy-buttons</a> and if you use SASS and Compass you should know about fancy-buttons.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>This blog will be my thoughts on the creative process, creativity, web design, computer graphics, poetry, and the like. I&#8217;ve spent most of my adult life creating stuff. I started out with poems and then moved onto harder things like short stories and finally web sites. In the end it&#8217;s all a poem if you really think about it.  Or it should be anyway. One of my biggest problems with the web is its lack of poetry. Every web page should be poetic as all hell.  Especially now that designers and developers shouldn&#8217;t be using tables to lay out the page.</p>

<blockquote><p>One should never put a poem inside of a table. It&#8217;s far too violent.</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
